nick.co.uk 2019-05-06

# NICKELODE

                NICKELODEON UK LIMITED’S PRIVACY POLICY FOR KIDS AND PARENTS
LAST UPDATED: May 25, 2018
Welcome! The information on this page contains our "Privacy Policy", which tells you about how
we collect, use, and share information you might share with us when you visit and use websites,
apps and other internet services offered by Nickelodeon UK Limited (we’ll call all of these
together the “Nick Sites”). It is important you read through this Privacy Policy, and please make
sure your parent(s) or guardian(s) read and discuss it with you too!
 Nickelodeon UK Limited determines how the information (or ‘data’) collected about you is used,
so we are called the “data controller”.
After you read the Privacy Policy, we hope you will understand:
     what information we collect from you when you visit and use Nick Sites;
     how we use that information;
     when that information may be shared with third parties;
     how you or your parent(s) or guardian(s) can control how your information is used; and
     how we store and protect your information.
Your privacy is very important to us. Younger visitors should always check with their parent(s) or
guardian(s) before entering information on any website or mobile application and we encourage
them, together with you and the rest of the family or household to discuss how your information
should be shared when you are online.
We may change this policy from time to time so when we do, we will post the latest version on
the Nick Sites. If we wish to use your information in a way that is different from what we say in
this Privacy Policy, we will contact you (and your parent(s)/guardian(s) as needed) to get your
consent.
                                              Summary
We would like you to read the entire Privacy Policy which contains all the details, but you might
find this quick summary helps to answer some important questions you may have about the Nick
Sites.
                                 In general, we collect two types of information:
                                     1. Information that you actively give to us. For example,
  WHAT INFORMATION DO
                                         when you enter a competition or a promotion; or you
  YOU COLLECT?
                                         send us your drawings, photos or other material, you
                                         might give us information so we know who you are and
                                         how to contact you.

                         2. Information we automatically collect about your
                              computer or other devices connected to the Internet.
                              This might be your IP address, a cookie ID or a device ID
                              – basically, any set of numbers or letters that lets us
                              know your computer or device is the one visiting the
                              Nick Sites).
                     For more details about the information we collect, please see
                     “The Information We Collect And How We Use It” section below.
                     We might use your information to:
                          reply to requests you send to us;
                          allow you to use certain features and services;
                          personalize your settings and the advertising you see on
                              the Nick Sites;
                          send special offers and promotions to you when you (or
                              your parent(s) or guardian(s) have given us permission
                              to do this;
HOW DO YOU USE MY         measure the way you (and other people) use the Nick
INFORMATION?                  Sites (for example, to see which parts of the Nick Sites
                              are the most popular) so that we can manage and
                              improve our services.
                     We don’t always do all these things, but we might use your
                     information in these ways when we are permitted by law.
                     For more details about how we use your information, please
                     see “The Information We Collect And How We Use It” section
                     below.
                     We do our best to protect your information against loss and
                     unauthorised access, and keep our security measures up to
                     date as cyber threats change. If you think an unauthorised third
                     party has accessed your information, please contact us
HOW DO YOU STORE MY
                     immediately. For more details on how to reach us, please see
INFORMATION?
                     the “Contact Us” section below.
                     For more details about how we store information, please see
                     “The Information We Collect And How We Use It” section below.
WHAT INFORMATION DO  We share your information with certain others (“third parties”)
YOU SHARE WITH OTHER in different situations, but only as permitted by the law. This
PEOPLE (“THIRD       information may include information you have actively provided

PARTIES”), AND FOR us, information we collected automatically from you or your
WHAT PURPOSES?     device, and information that does not directly identify you like
                   whether you are a boy or girl, or how you watch our
                   programmes.
                   As appropriate under the circumstances, and as permitted by
                   law, we may share that information with:
                           law enforcement officers or others as needed to protect
                            or defend our rights and the rights of others;
                           companies and people we hire to help us to operate the
                            Nick Sites;
                           with advertisers and other third parties so that we can
                            provide additional content, products or services;
                           with our business partners who sponsor a promotion or
                            competition or who offer a service or feature on the
                            Nick Sites; and
                           in the event of a corporate transaction.
                   Otherwise, we won’t share your information unless it is with the
                   consent of you or your parent(s) or guardian(s).
                   For more details about the way we share information with
                   other people, please see “The Information We Collect And How
                   We Use It” section below.
                   In some cases, yes they do. For example, some third parties
                   (with our permission) may collect and disclose certain device
                   identifiers, like IP address or cookie information, to help to
                   operate the Nick Sites. For example, when we are providing
                   content to you, or allowing features to run on the Nick Sites, or
DO OTHERS COLLECT
                   showing adverts, or use analytics and other tools to improve the
INFORMATION ON THE
                   quality and performance of the Nick Sites, we will need to allow
NICK SITES?
                   our business partners to collect that information.
                   For more details about third parties and the information they
                   collect, please see “The Information We Collect And How We
                   Use It” section below.
                   Under the law, you may be entitled to:
WHAT RIGHTS DO I         complain about or ask us to change the way we use your
HAVE?                       information;
                         ask to see the information we store about you;

                                         correct mistakes in your information;
                                         ask us to delete the information we store about you;
                                          and
                                         ask for a copy of the information we hold about you to
                                          take to another website, application or interactive
                                          service.
                                  If we obtained your or your parents’ or guardians’ consent to
                                  collect your information, you or your parent(s) or guardian(s)
                                  may withdraw that consent for the future collection of your
                                  data at any time.
                                  For more details about your rights and choices concerning your
                                  information, please see the “Your Rights” section below.
                                  The Nick Sites are made available by Nickelodeon UK Limited,
                                  which is the ‘data controller’ in charge of the way all personal
                                  information is used under this Privacy Policy. If you have any
                                  questions about the use of your information when you visit or
                                  use the Nick Sites, please contact us at:
                                  The Data Protection Officer
  WHO ARE YOU AND HOW             Nickelodeon UK Limited
  CAN I CONTACT YOU?              17-29 Hawley Crescent
                                  London
                                  NW1 8TT
                                  dataprivacyrights@viacom.com
                                  For more details about whom we are, please see the “Contact
                                  Us” section below.
I.       The Information We Collect and How We Use It
In this section, we explain what personal information we collect about you and how we collect it
when you visit the Nick Sites. You provide some of this information to us, and other types of
information we may collect automatically. You will only be required to share information that is
reasonably necessary to participate in the particular activity, so when information is required in
order to participate in activity, we will let you know.

Information you provide to us
You may be required to provide us information, for example, in order to register for a Site, or
participate in a promotion or competition. The information required varies by Site, but may
include: (a) first name and surname; (b) birth date; (c) gender; (d) country; (e) state; (f) postal
code; (g) user name and password; (h) mobile telephone number; (h) email address; or (i) other
profile information such as avatar preferences, communications preferences, and interests.
Information we automatically collect from your computer or device
When you come to one of our Sites, we may automatically collect certain information about your
use of the Site, including information about the websites you visited before and after visiting the
Site, the web pages and advertisements you viewed and any links you clicked on or within the
Sites, information collected through the use of unique identifiers such as cookies (see below),
information regarding your Internet Service Provider, and other standard server log information.
We also automatically collect information about your computer or mobile device, such as the
type of operating system (e.g., Windows, Mac, iOS, or Android), your IP address (a number
assigned by your Internet Service Provider that can identify your device), the type of web
browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome, and Firefox), unique device identifiers (or UDID,
a permanent identifier for certain mobile devices) or advertising identifiers (a resettable
identifier that is assigned to your mobile device by your operating system provider, such as Apple
or Google) and crash data), ("Computer Information").
Cookies and Tracking Technologies
We and our advertising and analytics service providers use cookies, which are small text files that
help store user preferences and activity, and similar technologies such as web beacons, pixels,
and ad tags to recognize you when you visit the Nick Sites (“Tracking Technologies”), and to
collect information such as the number of visits, which features or pages are popular,
measurements about an advertising campaign’s success, and other information about how you
use our services. This allows us to ensure our services are functioning properly, to improve our
services, and to provide and measure advertisements. For more information about cookies and
how to disable them, please visit our Cookies Policy: http://www.nick.co.uk/info/cookie-policy
How we use your information
We will only collect, store, or otherwise process your personal information in the following
situations:

       When we have your consent or the consent of your parent or guardian (such as allowing
        you to register for an account on one of our sites or to provide you with advertising or
        marketing materials). You or your parent or guardian can withdraw consent at any time,
        but keep in mind that withdrawing consent does not affect the legality of the processing
        of your data before the consent was withdrawn.
       We need to use your personal information to perform our responsibilities under a
        contract with you (e.g., providing the products or services you have requested, or
        allowing you to enter a promotion or a competition, or inform you that you’ve won).
       We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal information. For example, we
        may process your personal information to figure out what is most popular on the Nick
        Sites so we can make more things like it; to communicate with you about our services;
        and to prevent fraud or unlawful behaviour.
       We are required by law to process the information.
If you have questions about our processing or if you wish to withdraw consent you have
previously given us, please see the “Contact Us” section below.
II.     How We Store the Information We Collect
We maintain reasonable technical and organizational steps to help ensure that information
collected is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our
database servers and use of electronic security systems and password protections which guard
against unauthorized access. We limit access to visitor's information to employees and
contractors who are authorized for the proper handling of such information. We also take
reasonable steps to help make sure our third-party agents protect the security of your personal
data.
Information collected at the Nick Sites will not be stored for longer than is necessary for the
purposes described in this Privacy Policy, or to otherwise meet legal requirements.
III.    Information We Share with Third Parties
Sometimes we need third parties to carry out services for us. For example, if you win a
competition, we may need to pass your information to a third party to arrange delivery of your
prize, or we may need advice from an auditor or legal adviser. We currently use The Promotions
Factory Limited (company number 03687321) to assist us with competitions and our regular
email newsletter. We will make sure that these third parties keep your information secure; only
keep the information for so long as is necessary; and will comply with all applicable laws and
regulations.
Apart from the above, we may pass on your information to third parties in the following
circumstances:

        we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to comply with
         legal obligations;
        if disclosing the information is necessary to perform our responsibilities under a contract
         with you;
        in the context of any sale or transaction involving all or a portion of the business, or as
         may be required or permitted by law or required for the purposes of any regulatory audit
         to which we may be subject from time to time; and
        with your (or your parents’/guardians’) consent.
Finally, we share information that is generic and doesn’t identify you, such as whether you’re a
boy or girl and how you watch our programmes. We may use such information (in whole or in
part) to identify trends and may pass this to third parties, such as advertisers and business
partners to give them a better understanding of our business.
IV.      What Information Others May Collect
In accordance with applicable law, and with your consent or your parents’ or guardians’ consent,
where required, third parties may collect, use or disclose cookie information, IP addresses, or
other identifiers from devices and/or browsers of users who visit Nick Sites for the purposes of
supporting the operations of the Nick Sites, which can include, for example:
        providing content or allowing features to run on the Sites;
        serving advertising; and
        using analytics and other tools to improve the quality and performance of the Nick Sites.
Our corporate affiliates may also collect or maintain information through the Nick Sites to the
extent they provide any support for the Nick Sites or any of the services we offer you.
The Nick Sites also use a variety of third-party service providers such as advertising networks,
data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, and marketing analytics service
providers. While these third parties or advertisers, cannot access the Tracking Technologies that
we set, they may themselves set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your device if
you choose to have Tracking Technologies enabled in your browser. The use of such technology
by these third parties is within their control and not the Nick Sites. Even if we have a relationship
with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your
information and those sites may use the information they collect from you consistent with their
own privacy policies. For more information on how to disable Tracking Technologies, please see
our Cookies Policy: http://www.nick.co.uk/info/cookie-policy
V.       Your Rights

You have rights in relation to your personal data. In accordance with applicable law, these include
the right to:
  •   Request access to your personal data;
  •   Request correction of your personal data;
  •   Request deletion of your personal data;
  •   Object to processing of your personal data;
  •   Request restriction of processing your personal data; and
  •   Request a copy of certain personal data for reuse elsewhere.
If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please see the “Contact Us” section below.
We may need to request limited information from you to help us confirm your identity in order
for you to exercise any of your rights.
We generally do not charge a fee to exercise your rights. Nevertheless, if your request is clearly
unfounded, repetitive or excessive, in accordance with the law, we may charge a reasonable fee
or refuse to comply with your request.
If you believe that our processing of your personal data infringes applicable law, please see the
“Contact Us” section below. If we are not able to address your concern, you have the right to
lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Authority where you reside, where you work, or
where the infringement occurred. For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority,
please see: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-
authorities/index_en.htm.
VI.     International Transfers of Personal Data
We and our service providers transfer your personal information to, or store or access it in, other
countries where the laws may not provide levels of protection for your personal data equivalent
the protection provided by the laws of the European Union. When we do this, we take steps to
ensure that your personal data receives an appropriate level of protection through contractual
requirements imposed on the recipient of the information (you can obtain a copy of these
clauses by contacting us; please see the “Contact Us” section) or, when we transfer data to the
United States, through the EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks (“Privacy Shield”)
regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the
European Economic Area (EEA) or Switzerland to the United States. Our parent company is part
of the Viacom family of companies in the United States (including Viacom, Inc. and Viacom
International Inc.), which adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles, as described in Viacom’s
Privacy Shield certification, which you can find at https://www.privacyshield.gov/.
For any questions or complaints regarding our compliance with either the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield

Framework or the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, please contact us at
privacyshield@viacom.com. If we do not resolve your complaint, you may submit your complaint
free of charge to JAMS, Viacom’s designated independent dispute resolution provider based in the
United States. For information about the JAMS dispute resolution process or to submit a complaint,
please click here https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield to go to JAMS’ website. Under
certain conditions specified by the principles of the Privacy Shield you may also be able to invoke
binding arbitration to resolve your complaint. Viacom is subject to the investigatory and
enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. If Viacom shares personal information
collected in the EEA with a third-party service provider in the United States that processes the
information on Viacom’s behalf, Viacom will be liable for that third party's processing of personal
information in violation of the Privacy Shield, unless Viacom can prove that it is not responsible for
the unauthorized processing.
VII.     Contact Us
If you have any other questions about our information handling practices, including our practices
with respect to children's personal data, or would like further information regarding the Nick
Sites, please contact Nickelodeon UK Limited (which is the data controller of the information you
supply to the Nick Sites):
         The Data Protection Officer
         Nickelodeon UK Limited
         17-29 Hawley Crescent
         London
         NW1 8TT
         dataprivacyrights@viacom.com
